[{"answer": "Forty-seven.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "How old are you?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "Under your suit, I know that you look like that.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 21, "question": "You're -- you're a year old than me, and you look like this?", "qSentId": 20}, {"answer": "PhotoShop.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "Do you look that under your suit?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "Well, I literally had a week out.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "What did you think when you heard?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, my first response was that these families will maybe have some sort of closure to the extent that anyone can really have closure with the kind of things that families have gone through.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 83, "question": "What was going through your mind having had that odd connection?", "qSentId": 82}, {"answer": "Well, I went down to Times Square because I got a -- I just had a sense that people would be gathering and sharing this moment in history.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 90, "question": "And what's the first thing you did?", "qSentId": 89}, {"answer": "Well, I got on that flight.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 112, "question": "When you knew that you had been on a plane that had been used as -- as a dry run, how does it make you feel?", "qSentId": 111}, {"answer": "I think it's an April Fool's joke.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 125, "question": "And what is it?", "qSentId": 124}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "Did you have any memory of these guys being on the plane?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I -- you know, I loved politics more as a younger man.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Have you ever been tempted to have a proper run yourself?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "Well, it's funny.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 149, "question": "-- you have to be a conservative when you get older, right?", "qSentId": 148}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "In what way?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Well, that's true.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 221, "question": "So, it wouldn't actually be damaging, would it?", "qSentId": 220}, {"answer": "I love -- I helped Trump run.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "Does -- and what of that prospect?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "\"Declare a victory, and get off the field.\"", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "But, also, he was able to stand back at the end and say, \"Well, I forced out the truth,\" you know?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "I think it -- I think it's really hard.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 261, "question": "When you saw Matt say that, did you share a slight disappointment for President Obama or no?", "qSentId": 260}, {"answer": "(INAUDIBLE).", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "Don't you play, boy?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Listen, nobody is going to throw any charity events for me on this subject.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "I mean, what a problem I'd love to have, Mr. Lowe?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "See, by answering that question I implicitly agree with you.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 294, "question": "I mean, is it -- is it a double-edged sword being impossibly good looking?", "qSentId": 293}, {"answer": "Well, part of me is -- I'm a lot nerdier.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "What are you about?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "-- than you think.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "In what way?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "I think I'm amazed that that launched so many people.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "Well, the casting -- the man who cast that movie, whose voice was on the clip we just heard is a man named Fred Ruse, (ph) who cast \"Godfather I,\" \"Godfather II,\" and \"Star Wars,\" and \"American Graffiti,\" and \"The Outsiders.\"", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "I mean, no movie could have ever launched quite as many huge stars as that?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Do you -- do you stay in touch with any of that cast?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "You know, it's more like the people that you go to college with, and who were in your dorm.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Friends with them?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 347, "question": "Are there any you would just ring up for a chat?", "qSentId": 346}, {"answer": "Really to get a part of this, you have to get a little damaged.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 364, "question": "It's quite a barbaric business, isn't it?", "qSentId": 363}, {"answer": "And you can almost chart the parallel.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 370, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 369}, {"answer": "Yes -- no.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 377, "question": "It's fascinating, isn't it?", "qSentId": 376}, {"answer": "I -- like I said, I really believe that it's so fulfilling to connect with an audience on stage, on -- on screen; however you're doing it.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 382, "question": "That that's why so many people that go through that kind of thing?", "qSentId": 381}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 419, "question": "You didn't actually do that?", "qSentId": 418}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "That's what you actually did?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "I did a little research, and I came up with a phone number, and I called her at the Pentagon.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "And then what happened?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 427, "question": "You didn't?", "qSentId": 426}, {"answer": "The rest is history.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 429, "question": "And?", "qSentId": 428}, {"answer": "My motto into this day is: go big, or go home.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "I mean, not only women who were the hottest dates to be had, you were on a bit of a mission, weren't you, to be like the stud of your generation?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 460, "question": "Do you think everybody has that devil in them basically?", "qSentId": 459}, {"answer": "You know what, I'm going to agree with you.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 464, "question": "Right?", "qSentId": 463}, {"answer": "That's the definition of a Sophie's choice.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 467, "question": "Which one would you least rather go through again?", "qSentId": 466}, {"answer": "Well, I would take the sex tape off the list, because it led me to get sober, which changed my life.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 469, "question": "If I could say to you you've got to go through one of these again, which would you least rather go through again?", "qSentId": 468}, {"answer": "It's a culture.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 483, "question": "Do you understand why people are obsessed with celebrities doing that kind of thing, or being caught doing that kind of thing?", "qSentId": 482}, {"answer": "Once you go through your turn in the barrel, you have a unique perspective on it.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 485, "question": "Do you look at other people and enjoy their own scandals, downfalls and so on, in the way that others have enjoyed yours over the years?", "qSentId": 484}, {"answer": "There's a part of me that admires that, that admires resolutely living his life.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 502, "question": "When you see someone like him resolutely refusing to play the traditional game, what do you think?", "qSentId": 501}, {"answer": "Oh yes, sure.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "Do you worry about him?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "You know, I hope not.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 526, "question": "Do you fear that one day you're going to wake up and something awful will have happened?", "qSentId": 525}, {"answer": "Well, I think I was probably living a life that was not as satisfying as I was pretending it to be.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 537, "question": "Why did you need to do that?", "qSentId": 536}, {"answer": "Also, I think it's probably really satisfying for a while.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 540, "question": "But when you actually get it, it's not quite what it's cracked up to be?", "qSentId": 539}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 552, "question": "Would you try everything once?", "qSentId": 551}, {"answer": "I didn't -- this is the '80s.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "Where did you draw the line?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "A lot of it was.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Was it that good?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "If I thought I could go out and do what I used to do and have fun, I would do it in two seconds.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 574, "question": "Do you ever miss it?", "qSentId": 573}, {"answer": "OWE: It was great.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Or was it cathartic?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "Well, when I met her -- I met her and she was my makeup artist on \"Bad Influence,\" a movie that I did, a good movie.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 615, "question": "Tell me about Cheryl, your wife, because she came along just when you need someone like her, didn't she?", "qSentId": 614}, {"answer": "She saw me unlike any other woman that had been in my orbit for years.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "For someone who doesn't know her, what are her qualities that particularly got you?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "I was -- that I was the biggest loser ever, that I had blown this chance with somebody who truly loved me.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 637, "question": "What were you thinking when she did that?", "qSentId": 636}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 641, "question": "When you see contemporaries, many of them, who fall off the rails and go through wives and women and just never seem to find this kind of contentment, do you feel very, very lucky that you just managed to stumble across somebody that was perfect for you?", "qSentId": 640}, {"answer": "Yeah, we were off the air for a couple months, but now we're back.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 665, "question": "You mean, we haven't been on TV?", "qSentId": 664}, {"answer": "No, I did not (EXPLETIVE DELETED) know that.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 667, "question": "You knew that, right?", "qSentId": 666}, {"answer": "Rob, this is good news.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "How long have I not been (EXPLETIVE DELETED) on television?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "The truth was -- and I think people who work for big corporations will get this.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 679, "question": "What was the truth?", "qSentId": 678}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 688, "question": "Do you ever regret it?", "qSentId": 687}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 693, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 692}, {"answer": "Listen, I've been blessed.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "The greatest moment of your life?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "1999 till now.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 714, "question": "Which era is when you've been at your happiest?", "qSentId": 713}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110506pmt", "aSentId": 721, "question": "The business?", "qSentId": 720}]